Miyo-chan!
It'll be alright.
The party's starting soon.
I'm sorry.
Are you nervous?
I've never worn a dress before.
Will I even be able to walk properly in this?
Don't be silly!
It looks great on you.
Plus, you studied so hard for this.
Believe in yourself, you've got this!
Thank you, Hazuki-san.
That's my girl.
If I'm not on my best behavior...
I'm going to embarass Kiyoka.
I have to do my best!
Miyo!
Kiyoka-sama.
Thank you for waiting for me.
Um, Kiyoka-sama...
What do you think?
You're stunning.
Thank you!
You look quite handsome as well.
How forward of you.
I'm sorry!
Shall we?
Yes!
Kiyoka Kudou's new fiancée is from the Saimori Clan...
Saimori isn't a name you hear often these days.
I wonder what she's like.
This is their first time making a public appearance together.
Is that…
Um...
What is it?
I... feel like I've already made some kind of mistake.
I can feel everyone staring at me.
You haven't made any mistakes.
Today is just a casual gathering.
It's a chance for everyone to make their introductions.
Miyo-chan!
Hazuki-san.
Still nervous?
Your etiquette is perfect.
You'll be fine!
Thank you!
Mother!
Mother?
Let me introduce you.
This is my son, Asahi.
We're living separately now.
I see him once a month.
It's nice to meet you.
That's no good.
You have to bow low like this.
Hey, Asahi!
Sorry about that, Miyo-chan!
He's not used to this kind of thing yet.
Yes I am!
Things have really changed, haven't they?
I've never seen the captain look that kind.
Would it kill him to be nicer to me too?
This is simply splendid...
Listen!
Well, certainly...
He seems to have a different air about him.
Yeah?
In front of Miyo he's a completely different man.
Give me a break!
To think meeting someone could change a man that much.
Was my introduction earlier incorrect?
Kids will be kids.
Pay it no mind.
Miyo, do you have a moment?
What is it?
There's someone I want you to meet.
Follow me.
Alright.
How's the party so far?
Are you getting used to it?
Yes, somehow.
There's no need to be too self-conscious.
The night breeze will help you relax a bit.
Okay.
Kiyoka, you came.
Thank you for waiting.
Good to see you.
It's been awhile, Takaihito-sama.
Come, sit with me.
This must be the Saimori girl, then.
That's right.
It's a pleasure to meet you. My name is Miyo Saimori.
Before you is...
The Emperor's second son.
Blessed with the Gift of Divine Revelation, this is Takaihito-sama.
Hey now...
I came here today because I wanted to talk to the daughter of the Saimori Clan...
...and to explain the disturbances at the Royal Burial Grounds.
I am truly sorry to have inconvenienced you.
The Usuba Clan, the Saimori Clan...
They all had their lives disrupted by my father.
What in the world is this about?
All of it was orchestrated by the Emperor.
Truly pathetic, but it is what it is.
Why would he do such a thing?
My father was particularly afraid of Dream Sight.
The strength of this Gift depends on its user.
It is said that Dream Sight surpasses even the power of Divine Revelation.
Nonetheless, if there were no Dream Sight user...
The Usuba clan would pose no threat.
However, Sumi Usuba was born with the Gift of Telepathy.
With this, the possibility of a Dream Sight user being born came to pass.
My father believed the purer the blood of the Usuba, the likelier a gifted birth.
He moved to block Sumi's marriage in the Usuba clan.
He worked from behind the scenes.
He pulled the strings of the Tsurugi Trading Company in his favor.
The Usuba Clan grew weak.
At the same time, being unable to produce any gift users,
the Saimori clan was in decline.
Baiting them with money and the unique ability of the Usuba, he married Sumi off to the Saimori Clan.
He succeeded in separating her from the Usuba Clan.
And then, into the Saimori Clan,
a daughter was born. You.
Even so...
The head of the Saimori Clan apologized when he learned you did not manifest a gift.
After that revelation, he married you off to Kudou.
That changed everything.
I think I have a handle on it.
Once Miyo was released from the Saimori Clan, the seal was broken.
His Majesty must have discovered Miyo had awakened her Gift.
So we were the targets of the Royal Burial Ground incident?
That's correct.
Now, with your engagement set in stone,
you posed an even greater threat to my father.
It was to keep us apart.
However, there's another reason my father went to such great lengths...
Keep this between us.
The emperor has already lost the Gift of Divine Revelation.
He must've been under immense pressure.
Abandoning all his political machinations.
Exhuming the Royal Burial Grounds.
Drawing everyone into his plan, he wanted you gone.
It makes my blood boil.
My father needlessly sacrificed the lives of innocents for his own convenience.
Both Saimori and Usuba, forced to cooperate, became victims.
All because of my father's selfishness.
So then the Usubas won't be charged with a crime?
Correct.
Your life has changed a lot because of my father.
I am truly sorry.
Despite that, I was able to meet Kiyoka-sama.
In this moment, I am truly blessed.
Is that so?
It is.
I'm glad we got to chat this evening.
I'll see you soon.
Of course!
I never thought you'd be able to talk with Taikaihito-sama so openly.
You were genuine.
Thank you!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
My word, that child...
Miyo-chan, I'm so sorry!
It's fine.
Alright, crisis averted.
Asahi!
Father.
That's right, I never introduced you.
This is my ex-husband.
And now you know.
I apologize.
I've been out of contact.
I've been busy too, so we're even.
Hey, Asahi!
Come here.
You've been in a bad mood all day.
Oh, is that so?
When he met Miyo, he was acting strange.
Asahi, what's the most important thing to remember when meeting someone for the first time?
To smile.
That's right!
So if you're always sulking like that,
Miyo-chan's not going to like you!
That's fine, I mean...
I hate Miyo-san anyway!
Miyo-san stole mom. That's why I hate her!
Is that right?
The truth is Hazuki and I see each other once a month.
Recently, Hazuki has been talking a lot about Miyo-san.
It seems like Asahi didn't like that.
I never thought it would lead to something like this.
He was just jealous of Miyo-chan.
My little goofball.
This is how much I love my Asahi.
Then who do you love more, Miyo or me?
Do you love your father?
I love him.
Do you love me?
Lots!
Then who do you love more, your father or me?
You will always have a special place in my heart, Asahi.
But, Miyo-chan is very important to me, too.
You both are family to me.
Miyo-san is family, too?
Yes, that's right.
Even though we live apart, we're still family.
Miyo-chan may not be related by blood,
but I'm so proud of my little sister.
Thank you so much.
Hazuki-san...
I...
I'm proud of my sister, too.
Yes!
Yes, that's it!
Thank you! That's what I'm talking about!
That's why, Asahi.
Please be kind to Miyo-chan.
Um...
I'm sorry I ruined your dress.
Still...
It's so precious you were jealous of Miyo-chan.
Too tight, mom!
Enough!
Just as family can take on many forms,
so too can happiness.
Even now, somewhere, true happiness is being born.
Surely, the future will deliver this happiness.
Our happiness.
I wonder if I've been able to convey this to Miyo.
Could she sense it?
Even just a little bit?
Together, we'll discover a new happiness.
Miyo.
Good morning!
Whoops!
Excuse me!
H-here...
Thank you.
So, what are you doing here?
Pardon the intrusion.
I'm just here to make a proposal.
Would you like to hire me as Miyo's bodyguard?
What?
From now on,
Miyo will have to deal with the Gift of Dream Sight.
If only there were someone else who could protect her...
It could come in handy.
I was wondering what you were getting at.
I have to leave for work.
Miyo-chan!
Kiyoka!
I'm coming in!
What is it this time?
Good morning, Miyo-sama.
Good morning, Yurie-san.
It's just Yurie.
Hazuki, too? Why?
A-ha...
What's up with you?
It's been awhile.
Actually I'm just here to deliver a proposal to Kudou-san.
I'm inquiring about becoming Miyo's bodyguard.
That's reassuring.
They should be pleased!
Right!
I'm worn out from this morning.
Kiyoka-sama.
Your hair tie is loose.
Let me tie it for you.
Bend down, please.
Sorry, please go ahead.
All done.
Kiyoka-sama.
Um, could you please bend down once more?
Is something wrong?
I hope you do your best and work hard today.
Miyo...
Yes?
Why are you doing that?
Um...
I thought it might cheer you up.
You didn't like it?
I'm sorry!
That's not it.
It made me feel better.
Well, I'm off.
Have a good day!
As for the happy times...
In the blink of an eye,
before you know it,
Summer has already turned to fall.
Kiyoka-sama has given me a new perspective...
For the first time, I am able to see true happiness.
It is my precious treasure.
From now on...
I want to weave a tale together.
To walk together.
I'm absolutely sure...
...it will be my true happiness.